bplay.com 2014-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Magmic

Magmic Inc. and its affiliated companies (“Magmic Games”), are committed to protecting the privacy of our users and customers. We consider the security of personal information to be of the highest importance, and have established standards to maintain and guard against unauthorized access to user information. The following policy (“Privacy Policy”) outlines how Magmic Games collects personal information and what we do with the information once it is collected.

Should you have any questions relating to our Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy[a]magmic.com or at Magmic Inc. 126 York Street, Ottawa, ON Canada K1N 5T5.

### What this Privacy Policy covers

This Privacy Policy applies to personal information collected through its mobile and online products, online services and website(s) including, but not limited to Magmic Games’ games (together “Services”). It applies only to personal information collected on and after the date that this Privacy Policy is posted.

### What types of information do we collect?

**Information you provide us**  
While we do not require any personal information to visit our website, we may at times request some personal information, such as your e-mail address, in order to provide updates about our products and services and our websites. We may also ask visitors to indicate if they would like to receive updates from Magmic Games or its divisions, and if so, what types of information they would like to receive. Some areas of our Services require login information (such as user name and password) to be created and/or entered at some point in the visit. Finally, our sites contain retail areas that require the entry of personal and financial information such as first and last name, credit card information, and billing address information. In summary, we may request and may or may not store any of the following pieces of personal information depending on the nature of the visit to our sites:

  * e-mail address
  * user name/alias
  * password
  * communication preferences (topics of interest, type of communication, etc.)
  * first/last name
  * credit card information (type, account number, expiry date, etc.)
  * billing address information
  * phone number

We may also occasionally request non-personal information such as your phone platform, carrier, age group, and other information that may or may not be associated with your personal information.

### Information we may collect through technology

We collect certain types of information as part of our normal website operations using a variety of technologies, including:

**Server Logs**  
When you visit our website, our web servers automatically collect information about each transaction between your device and our servers. This is a practice common to all web servers known as server logging. Server logs can contain, but are not limited to, your IP address (a number associated with your internet service provider, company, or educational institution), transaction date, browser type, request type (GET or POST), session IDs, and cookie information. This information is normally used to generate information about general usage on our site and to improve our website. It may or may not be associated with your personal information.

**Cookies, Beacons and Tracking**  
Magmic Games may use “cookies” and other technologies such as Flash cookies, HTML5, pixel tags, locally shared objects, clear GIFs and web beacons. We may use cookies and similar technologies for various purposes with our Services to enhance user experience and to provide information about general usage trends. We treat information collected by cookies and similar technologies as non-personal data.

**Cookies:**  are files stored on your computer by websites that you visit and are typically used to quickly identify your device and to “remember” you. Using your browser’s preferences, you can control how cookies are treated, which sites may use them on your device, and how you are notified of their use. Disabling cookies may affect your ability to use the Services.

**Flash cookies & HTML5:** are locally stored objects, which are small files similar to browser cookies and are used to remember your settings to personalize the look and feel of the Services. Locally shared objects only collect data in the aggregate. You may prevent locally shared objects from being placed by disabling locally stored objects in your browser or visit www.adobe.com. Locally stored objects, such as HTML5 Web Storage, are used for similar purposes as cookies but typically may contain a greater amount and different types of data than browser cookies.

**Web beacons and pixel tags:**  are electronic images that allow Magmic Games to count users who have visited certain pages or viewed certain advertisements. Web beacons, like cookies, do not include personal data. E-mails and other electronic communications Magmic Games sends to you may contain pixel tags that enables Magmic Games to track your usage of the communication, including whether the communication was opened and/or what links were followed (if any).

### Other types of information we may collect

**Non-personal data**  
“Non-personal data” means information that does not directly identify you. Non-personal data can also include “aggregate” and “de-personalized” information, which is data Magmic Games collects about the use of Magmic Games Services, from which any personally identifiable data has been removed.

Magmic Games may use third party analytical software or tools to automatically collect and use certain non-personal data that does not directly enable Magmic Games to identify you. The types of non-personal data Magmic Games may collect and use include, your device properties, IP address, Media Access Control (“MAC”) address and unique device identifier or other device identifier (“UDID”); your device software platform and firmware; who mobile phone carrier is; your geographical data, like zip code, area code and course location; your game progress, score and achievements; and other non-personal data as reasonably required by Magmic Games to enhance the Services and other Magmic Games products and services.

Magmic Games uses Google Analytics tool in order to develop and analyze use of the Services. If you wish to opt-out from Google Analytics, please follow these instructions:[http://support.google.com/googleanalytics/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=181881](http://support.google.com/googleanalytics/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=181881)

Magmic Games may use and disclose to Magmic Games’ partners and contractors the collected non-personal data for purposes of analyzing usage of the Services, advertisement serving, managing and providing the Services and to further develop the Services and other Magmic Games services and products.

You recognize and agree that the analytics companies utilized by Magmic Games may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other services or products relating to your activities. These companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.

**Ad Serving Technology**  
Magmic Games may employ third party ad serving technologies that use certain methods to collect information as a result of ad serving through Services. Magmic Games or third parties operating the ad serving technology may use demographic and location information as well as information logged from your hardware or device to ensure that appropriate advertising is presented within the Service. Magmic Games or third parties may collect and use data for this purpose including, but not limited to IP address (including for purposes of determining your coarse location), UDID, MAC, software, applications, hardware, browser information, internet and on-line usage information and in-game information. This data may be used and disclosed in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Policy of the company providing the ad serving technology.

The advertising companies who deliver ads for Magmic Games may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other services or products. These companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies. These ad serving technologies are integrated into Services; if you do not want to be subject to this technology, do not use or access Services. Although Magmic Games takes commercially reasonable steps to instruct such advertising companies to comply with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, Magmic Games does not have access to or control of third party technologies.

We reserve the right to request other types of information in the future.

### When we collect your information

Magmic Games will likely collect your information: when you register for Services, contests and special events; when you access Services through a third party ID, such as social networking sites or gaming services; when you subscribe to newsletters; when you purchase a product or Services through Magmic Games’ online stores or an apps store; when you use “Invite Friends”, “Send Your Friend a Gift” or other similar features on Magmic Games’ website, or on a social networking site or gaming service; when you request technical support; and when you otherwise use Magmic Games Services where we require personal data for participation.

### What we do with personal information

Magmic Games is committed to maintaining the privacy of our visitors and customers. Personal information that we collect either actively or passively from our visitors and customers is used only to conduct business, communicate with visitors and customers, improve our products and services, and improve our websites. In that regard, we may use personal information to send notifications or updates regarding the products and services of Magmic Games using electronic or non-electronic means. Newsletters and product notifications sent by Magmic Games include unsubscribe information which will remove you from all mailing lists permanently or until such time as you request this status to be changed. Magmic Games will not sell, trade, share, or in any way communicate personal information we store about you with any third party without your permission, with certain exceptions (see Exceptions, below).

### Exceptions

Certain exceptions apply to our policy of sharing personal information with third parties.

**Business transactions**  
In order to conduct business transactions on our retail websites, we must transmit purchase information to a third-party for credit card processing. We may also transmit device information to third-party vendors of products sold through Magmic Games retail sites. We are committed to working only with reputable third-parties for these services, but are not responsible for the storing, maintenance, or protection of personal information by third parties once the information leaves our systems. By using our retail sites you acknowledge that some personal information may be exchanged with third parties in the normal course of business and indicates that you grant Magmic Games permission to share the necessary information with third parties in order to conduct business with you.

**Legal and safety factors**  
We may disclose personal information if required by law (for example, to comply with a subpoena or mandatory legislation) or in the event that we need to share information with a third party in order to protect your safety and security or the safety and security of Magmic Games, its divisions, or its employees.

**Corporate Change**  We may disclose your personal data to third parties in connection with a corporate change, including any due diligence process, but such disclosure will be subject to Privacy Policy continuing to govern treatment of personal data.

### You Are Responsible

You should be aware of the open nature of certain social networking and other open features of the Services Magmic Games may make available to you. You may choose to disclose data about yourself in the course of contributing user generated content to the Services. Any data that you disclose in any of these forums, blogs, chats or the like is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality. Magmic Games is not responsible for any personal data you choose to make public in any of these forums.

If you are under 18 years of age or a minor in your country of residence, ask your legal guardian’s permission to use or access the Services. Magmic Games takes children’s privacy seriously, and encourages parents and guardians to play an active role in their children’s online experience at all times.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may change at any time. You should review this policy periodically to refresh your knowledge of our policy and to note changes that may have been made.
